- 干杯   - 干杯
- Cheers.     - Cheers.
你全身泡泡好可爱
You look cute in bubbles.
你喝太多眼花了
Ahh, you're just all liquored up.
是我 我进去了
Hey, it's me. I'm coming in.
我今天上班累死了
I've had a very long, hard day.
我要去买炸鸡 你要不要？
Want some chicken?
不了 谢谢 再见
No, thanks. No chicken. Bye-bye.
你确定？炸鸡喔？不要海鲜饭或豆子？
You sure? Some extra-crispy, dirty rice?
我最后一次说我不要了 出去 乔伊
For the last time, no! Get out, Joey!
知道了
All right.
你没事吧？抱歉 他死都不走
Are you okay? He wouldn't leave.
缠着我问要不要炸鸡
He kept asking me if I wanted chicken.
炸鸡？
Chicken?
我想吃炸鸡
I could eat some chicken.
乔伊
Hey, Joe!
我要三块鸡 卷心菜 豆子 可乐
Could I get a, uh, three-piece, some coleslaw, some beans and a Coke?
健怡可乐
Aah! Diet Coke.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
- 早安 菲比   - 我非告诉你们不可
- Morning, Pheebs.     - I have to tell you this story.
刚才载我来的司机…
I was coming over and this cabdriver...
那人是不是叫做安格斯？
Was his name Angus?
什么？
What?
我们在伦敦遇到的计程车司机
He was a cabdriver we had in London.
哦 哈 哈 哈
Oh. Ha, ha, ha.
好吧 总之…
All right. Anyway...
他载我们去的酒馆叫什么？
What was that pub he took us to?
麦子酒馆
The Wheat Sheaf!
那里有一种啤酒…
And they had that beer...
- 伯丁罕   - 就是伯丁罕
- Boddington's.     - Boddington's.
菲比有话要说
Ooh, uh, Pheebs was going to tell a story.
他的帽子很好笑
So he had a really funny hat.
我不想说了
I don't want to talk about it.
- 嘿   - 嘿 罗斯
- Hey.     - Hey, Ross!
伯丁罕
Boddington's!
是啊
Oh, man!
若是能再喝一杯要我走回伦敦都行
I'd walk back to London for another frosty one of those bad boys.
世贸附近的英国酒馆好像有
They have them at the British pub by the Trade Center.
回头见
Later!
瑞秋不是应该回来了吗？
Shouldn't Rachel be back?
可是班机误点
Her plane got delayed.
不过现在也该到了
But she should be here by now.
你跟她通过电话 她很生气吗？
So you talked to her? Did she sound mad?
不会 那是因为她喜欢我
No. But she likes me.
你丢下她独自飞到希腊去
You abandoned her on a plane to Greece.
我才没有丢下瑞秋
I did not "abandon" Rachel. Okay?
艾蜜莉出现在机场
Emily showed up at the airport.
我当然得去追她 我别无选择
I had to go after her. I did what I had to do.
毕竟瑞秋是我太太
She's my wife. Rachel is my wife.
是艾蜜莉
Emily!
艾蜜莉是我老婆
Emily is my wife.
我是怎么了？
Man, what is that?
你还没有艾蜜莉的消息？
You haven't heard from Emily?
我在机场追丢之后就没有了
Not since I lost her at the airport.
她竟然跑得比你快
I can't believe she can outrun you.
她是飞毛腿 好吗？
Hey! She's fast, okay?
你自以为能打败我？我们现在就去外头较量
You think you can beat me? Let's go! Outside!
嗨
Hi!
嗨 瑞秋
Hi! Rachel!
瑞秋 我很抱歉 非常对不起你
Rach, I am so sorry. I am so, so sorry.
罗斯 你没做错
Come on. You just did what you had to do.
嗨 菲比
Hi, Pheebs.
就这样？你不生气？你应该很火大
That's it? You're not mad? It must've been terrible.
火大？我可是在希腊
Terrible? Hell, I was in Greece!
那间饭店非常棒 海滩很美 人又和善
There was a nice hotel, nice beach, met the nice people.
对我瑞秋来说可不差
It's not too shabby for Rachel.
就这样？
So, what, that's it?
对 我没生你的气
Well, yeah. We're cool. Totally cool.
谢谢 你真好
Thanks, Rach. You're the best.
你才好呢
Oh, no. You're the best.
我要去花店一趟
Oh, I got to go to the flower store.
大家都不肯说艾蜜莉在哪里
No one will tell me where Emily is...
我决定买72朵长茎红玫瑰 送去艾蜜莉爸妈家
...so I'm sending 72 long-stemmed, red roses to her parents' house.
每朵代表我认识她 并且深爱她的每一天
One for each day I've known and loved her.
她一定会感动的软化
That should get her talking.
罗斯 写卡片时别忘了 对方是"艾蜜莉"
When you make out the card, be sure to make it out to "Emily."
太好了 幸好你在希腊玩得开心
It's good that you had such a good time in Greece.
什么？
What?
我在希腊才不开心
I didn't have a good time in Greece!
罗斯丢下我一人
Ross abandoned me!
我买不到机票回来 只好住在他们的蜜月套房
I couldn't get a plane out. I had to stay in their suite!
每个人都要来问我 "盖勒太太 你哭什么？"
People came up to me going, "Mrs. Geller! Why are you cry?"
简直丢死人了
I mean, it was so humiliating!
我真是个白痴
I felt like such an idiot!
这都是我的错 你们知道为什么吗？
It's all my fault. You know why?
因为我的决定都不对
Because I make very bad decisions.
不要这么说
Oh, that's not true.
就是这样 我没胡说 我跑去伦敦追罗斯
Yes, it is true. I went after Ross in stupid London!
伦敦是个坏地方
London is stupid! Stupid!
我根本不该去伦敦
I should've never gone to London.
从今开始由你帮我做决定
From now on, you make all my decisions for me.
不行 我以前就这么做过
Oh, no. I did that for someone once.
我不喜欢主宰别人的生活
I'm not comfortable having that power over someone's life.
那我来
I'll do it.
很好 摩妮卡 以后由你主宰我的爱情生活
Fine. Monica, you are now in charge of my love life.
好 我该去上班了
Okay. I got to go to work.
瑞秋 很高兴看到你回来
And, uh, Rachel, great to have you back.
菲比
Pheebs!
看到你真开心
Always a pleasure.
(中央咖啡厅)
瑞秋 你看
Rachel? Sweetie, look.
这是你跟乔伊在招待会的照片
Here's a cute picture of you and Joey.
他已经结婚了
He's married.
罗斯结婚了 我到现在还不敢相信
Ross is married. I still can't believe it.
亲爱的 抓旁边就好
Honey, sweetie, by the edges.
看来我只好接受事实
I'll just have to accept it.
这都要怪我
I mean, it's my fault.
别抓中间 指纹会弄脏照片
Edges! Fingers! Smudgy!
天啊
Oh, my God!
算了 我知道你心情低落
That's okay. I know that you're very upset right now.
不是故意找我麻烦
I know that wasn't about me.
我看她就是跟她作对
I bet it was about her a little.
你要是肯放下罗斯一分钟
If you'd stop thinking about Ross...
就会发现到处有帅哥
...you'd notice there are great guys everywhere.
你看 例如阿甘
Look. Gunther.
他既善良又可爱
He's nice. He's cute.
阿甘的确…
Yeah. I guess Gunther is...
还有那边那个家伙
What about that guy over there?
记得吗？你以前跟他打情骂俏过
That's the guy you flirted with at the counter.
我不知道…
Oh, I don't know. I don't know.
你要和他谈谈
You're going to talk to him.
我们说好由我发号施今 我命令你去跟他说话
I make your decisions, and I say you're going to talk to him.
好吧
All right.
你说了算 看来我只好照办
You're the boss. I got to do what you tell me.
他听到这句话肯定上钩
Say that to him, and you're golden.
- 嘿   - 嗨
- Hey.     - Hey.
菲比 伦敦的照片洗出来了
Hey, Pheebs. We got our pictures back from London.
这张是所有人在伦敦塔拍的
Here's all of us at the Tower of London...
大家都在照片中
Here we all are.
有罗斯 乔伊 你…
There's Ross and Joey and you and...
和我
And me.
你一定听烦我们说伦敦的事了
We've been talking about London too much.
是我不好 因为我去不了
Sorry, it's just because I couldn't be there.
我只能大着肚子 烦都快烦死了
All I get to do now is pregnant stuff. It bums me out.
- 可怜啊…   - 真抱歉
- I'm sorry.     - Sorry.
- 怎么样？ - 总之我们东扯西扯
- What happened?     - A little of this, a little of that.
明天晚上要出去约会
I got myself a date tomorrow.
看吧？你就要忘记罗斯了
See? Didn't I tell you? You're getting over Ross already.
滚出去
Get out.
(我们有权利拒绝服务)
你怎么去那么久？
What took so long?
公事担搁了 不过我明天就辞职
I got caught up at work. But I'm quitting tomorrow.
谢谢你邀我过来
So thanks for having me over.
瑞秋
Rach...
菲比
Pheebs...
再见
See you, man.
他发什么神经？
What the hell was that?
可能在伦敦学到的欧洲风俗
Probably some European goodbye thing he picked up in London.
那才不是欧洲风俗
That's not European.
比较像法式热吻
It felt French.
我玩得好开心
I really had a good time.
我也是
Yeah, me too.
- 那么…   - 那么…
- So...     - So...
看来今天要结束了
I guess this is it.
是啊
Yeah, um...
- 除非你想进来？ - 好
- Unless you want to come inside?     - Yeah!
等等 我无法自做主张
Oh, uh, wait a minute. You know what? I can't decide this.
等我一下
Okay. Just hold on a second.
嗨
Um, hi.
Hi.
摩妮卡在吗？我有事要问她
Where's Monica? I have to ask her something.
她去洗衣服
Doing her laundry.
那是什么？
What's that?
我今天收到的包裹
It came in the mail today.
72朵长茎红玫瑰
It's 72 long-stemmed, red roses.
每朵代表我认识她 并且深爱她的每一天
One for each day I've known and loved Emily...
给剪成碎片
...cut up into mulch.
真是糟糕
Honey, that's awful.
还好啦
It's not so bad.
摩妮卡要用来做香料
Monica's going to make potpourri.
我要去淋雨散散心
I think I'm going to go wander out in the rain for a while.
外面没下雨
It's not raining.
连老天都不赏脸
I can't catch a break.
罗斯 你哪也别去 就坐这里
You're not going anywhere. Sit right here.
我们喝茶聊天
I'll make you some tea and we'll talk this out.
好吗？
All right?
好
Okay.
- 大卫   - 怎么样？
- Hey, Dave.     - Yeah.
改天再请你进来 我的室友病得很重
Um, I need to take a rain check. My roommate is really sick.
好 再见
Okay. Bye.
听着
Honey, listen.
我知道事情成这样很糟
I know things seem so bad...
看起来不会好…
...and that they won't get any...
我可以跟你谈谈吗？
Could I talk to you?
我掉了几只袜子
I dropped some socks.
耶
Yeah.
你又想老调重弹？又想跳回去自找苦吃？
What is the matter with you? Do you want to fall into the trap?
你根本没掉袜子
You did not drop any socks!
我刚碰到大卫 他说你打发他走
I saw Dave, and he said you blew him off!
你给我听好
You listen to me!
我要你离开罗斯去追大卫
I'm calling the shots! I say you leave Ross and go get Dave.
你到底想怎么样？
What are you doing?
其实我想… 我打算…
Well, ultimately I was trying, you know, I wanted...
告诉他我还爱他
...to tell him that I'm still in love with him.
什么？你不准说
What? You cannot tell him that!
为什么？
Why? Why not?
大家都喜欢听到这种话
People love to hear that!
这里由我做决定 我不准你说
I make the decisions and I say no!
你知道吗？你不能帮我做决定 因为…
You know what? No, you don't make my decisions, because...
我要开除你
...you're fired.
你不能开除我
You can't fire me.
你的事情由我来决定 我说我没被开除
I make your decisions, and I say I'm not fired. Ha!
既然如此…
Well...
瑞秋 让我进去
Rachel! Come on, let me in!
怎么了？
Having some trouble?
瑞秋把我锁在门外
Rachel locked the door.
你肯亲我 我就帮你撞开
I'll kick that door in if you give me some sugar.
瑞秋 让我进去
Rachel! Let me in!
谢谢
Thank you.
瑞秋 我可以跟你谈谈吗？
Rachel? Can I talk to you outside for a sec?
不可以
No.
我真的有话要跟你说
We really need to talk.
那就说啊
Well, then talk.
那我就说了
Okay, I will.
记得我们刚说你要做的事吗？
Remember that thing we just discussed that you wanted to do?
记得
Yes.
什么事？
What thing?
瑞秋要去学摇摆舞
Rachel wants to take swing dance lessons.
我非常不赞成
Which I think is a really stupid idea.
因为这种舞很危险 她一定学不会
It's dangerous. She won't get what she wants.
而且搞不好还会撞伤人
And who knows who she might end up hurting?
摩妮卡说得对 摇摆舞有点危险
Monica's right. Swing dancing can be tricky.
我要打电话
I have to use the phone.
我要取消五只 送给艾蜜莉的熊宝宝
I got to cancel those five, giant teddy bears I sent to Emily.
否则熊宝宝难逃死劫
My God. Think of the massacre.
我就是要说
I'm going to do it.
我知道你认为我疯了
I know you think I'm crazy.
但是在你告诉他之前 至少找到一个…
But before you tell him, try to find one person...
同意你想法的人 我打赌你找不到
...who thinks it's a good idea. I bet you can't.
拜托
Please?
好吧
All right. Fine.
乔伊 我已经进来了
Joey! I'm in!
那好
All right. Good deal.
菲比 嘿
Pheebs! Hey!
菲比？怎样？
Uh, Pheebs?  Yeah?
你上次说你都不能去伦敦
Um, you know how you were saying you didn't get to go to London...
觉得自己遭大家遗弃   - 如何？
...and you were feeling left out?     - Yeah.
我们很愧疚
Well, we all felt really bad about that...
决定大家一起去旅行
...so we decided to take a little trip together.
太好了
Oh, that's so nice!
太棒了 要去哪里？
How great! Where's the trip?
- 我们可以一起去野餐
- Well, we thought we would all go to a picnic...
就去中央公园   - 中央公园？
...in Central Park!     - Central Park?
对 大家一起去个一整天
All of us. All day.
什么鸟地方？
That sucks!
那根本不算旅行 我才刚从公园过来
That's not a trip! I just came from there.
大家去中央公园有什么好兴奋
What'll we high-five about at the stupid park?
好耶 就在我家旁边
It's right by my house. All right!
我决定回家反省这个烂主意
I'm going home to bask in the triumph of my Central Park idea.
等一下 热吻先生
Hold on a sec there, Mr. Kissy.
我一直想跟你讨论
I wanted to talk to you about...
你新学的欧洲民情
...this whole new European thing you've got going on.
你搞得我非常不自在
And I need to say it makes me very uncomfortable...
拜托你别再亲了
...and I just, you know, just stop it!
我只是想介绍大家认识欧洲文化
Just bringing some culture to the group.
只要不要介绍到我嘴里就好了
That's fine. Just don't bring it in my mouth.
我都快吐了
It makes me want to puke.
各位 菲比来了
Hey, everybody! Pheebs is here!
菲比  大家好
Phoebe! Whoo!  Okay. Whoo! Hi!
菲比 我们认为野餐的主意…
Pheebs, we decided that the picnic idea was a little...
实在烂透了
It didn't have any... Well, it blew.
所以今天下午决定 到大西洋城…
We thought that this afternoon we'd all go away for the whole weekend...
去度周末
...to Atlantic City.
大西洋城 太好了 谁想到的？
Ooh, Atlantic City! Oh, that's a great plan! Whose plan was that?
我
Mine!
- 等等 是我提议的   - 错
- Wait. It was my plan.     - No...
我说我们应该想个新的计划
...I said we needed a new plan.
然后我想到要去大西洋城
And I came up with Atlantic City.
这就是新的计划啊
Which is the new plan.
大家一小时后楼上见
Why don't we, um, all meet upstairs in an hour?
好的
Okay.
我要去打包了 我要摇着大屁股好好打包
I'm going to go pack. I'm going to go pack my ass off.
我们走吧
Let's go.
我等一下再上去找你
You know what? I'll meet you in a minute.
不行 瑞秋 没有人支持你 所以你不能说
Rachel, you didn't find anyone, so you can't tell him.
无所谓
You know what? That doesn't matter.
你知道对方不能回应你的爱意
Do you know how painful it is to tell someone you love them...
会有多痛苦吗？
...and not have them say it back?
我不在乎
I don't care.
好吧
Okay...
可是我看不下去
I can't watch.
你在看什么？
What you reading?
报纸
Paper.
上面说了什么？
Yeah? What's it about?
世界各地的新闻
The events from around the globe.
是啊
Okay...
我有件事要告诉你
Uh, there's something I have to talk to you about.
虽然大家都叫我别说
Everyone's saying I shouldn't.
但是他们都错了 有时候别人就是看不清楚
But I think they're wrong. People can be wrong.
有一次上班时
Once at work...
我说放射性碳测定法太老旧…
...I thought carbon dating is fossilized...
我说正经的
I'm really trying to tell you something here.
好…
Yeah...
说吧
Go ahead.
我这就说了
I think I'm just going to say it.
现在就告诉你
I'm just going to say it.
嗯…
Uh...
我还爱着你 罗斯
I'm still in love with you, Ross.
哇 嗯…
Wow, uh...
哈 我…
Huh. I'm...
我不知道现在该怎么回答
Wow. I'm not sure what to do with that right now.
怎么了？你跟我开玩笑？这就太恶劣了
What? Was that a joke? Because it's mean.
我很正经
I'm so dead serious.
不能再正经了
I'm totally serious.
那你笑什么？
Why are you laughing?
因为我刚听到自己的话
Because I just heard it!
我听到了 而且觉得很荒谬
I heard it! And it's ridiculous!
毕竟…
I mean...
你已经结婚
You're married!
你有老婆 我说这话太可笑
You're married, and it's just ridiculous.
我说话时似乎灵魂出壳
When I said it, I sort of floated up out of my body.
我的灵魂听到肉身说话
And then I heard myself say it, and then the floating Rachel...
灵魂认为 自己实在很白痴
I was like, "You are such an idiot!"
- 我的确已经结婚   - 我知道
- Well, I am married.     - I know.
虽然婚礼后就没跟老婆说过话
Though I haven't spoken to her since the wedding.
抱歉 这不好笑
I'm sorry. That's not funny.
其实还蛮好笑的
Actually, it kind of is.
我老婆不回我电话
My wife won't return my calls.
我不知道太太在哪里
I don't know where my wife is.
"罗斯 你老婆呢？" "我也不知道"
"Hey, Ross! Where's the missus?" "Don't know!"
天啊
Oh, God.
好
Okay.
你可以忘记我刚说的话吗？
You know what? Could you forget I told you this?
我不忘记也不行
Well, I kind of have to.
因为事实是…
Because the thing is...
事实就是你已经娶了艾蜜莉
The thing is, you know, that you're married to Emily.
事实正是如此
That is what the thing is.
天啊
Oh, God.
罗斯 我们还是好朋友吧 我说自己还爱你…
Things won't be weird between us, right? Was that stupid?
真是蠢毙了
Me telling you that?
不会 我很高兴你告诉我
No, no. I'm glad you did.
就算日子不顺利
If nothing else...
听到有人说爱你还是很开心
...it's always great when someone tells you they love you.
我早说过了
That's what I said!
- 谢谢你对我这么好   - 我才该谢谢你
- Thank you for being so nice.     - No. Thank you for...
谢谢你
Thank you.
- 大家走吧   - 前往大西洋城
- Okay, let's go!     - Yeah, Atlantic City!
走吧
Come on!
去大西洋城罗
Atlantic City, baby!
我们去大赌一笔 乔伊
Let's roll some bones. Hey, Joey!
赌博万岁
High-five for rolling bones.
- 啊   - 啊
- Ow!     - Ow!
哦
Oh.
Ooh!
菲比 你尿失禁？
Uh, Pheebs, you're leaking.
天啊 你羊水破了
Oh, my God. Your water broke.
对
Oh! Okay!
别放在心上 我要坐前座
Well, don't worry. I call shotgun.
菲比 我们得送你去医院
Pheebs, we have to take you to the hospital now.
菲比 你快要生了
Pheebs, the babies are coming now.
击掌 你要生了
Honey! High-five! The babies are coming!
哇
Whoo!
记不记得 我羊水破的那天？
Remember when my water broke?
菲比竟然快生了
Phoebe's going to have her babies.
我知道 真是太棒了
I know. It's beautiful and amazing.
我竟然每次离开 都得亲菲比跟瑞秋
I had to kiss Phoebe and Rachel every time I left the room.
可惜她们没看到我们嘿咻
It's too bad they didn't see us having sex.
你到底了不了解女人？
Do you know anything about women?
不了解
No.
- 算了   - 好
- It's all right.     - Okay.